ispot.tv 2014-02-14

# Privacy Policy - iSpot.tv

_Last Modified: November 19, 2012_

Your privacy is important to iSpot.tv, Inc. ("iSpot"). This privacy policy ("Policy") applies to the iSpot Web sites ("Sites"). This Policy explains how your personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by iSpot. 

## Personal Information Collected

We collect information from you in various ways when you use our Sites and Applications. We may collect personal information you directly provide on our Sites. In addition, we may collect personal information from you as a user of our Applications. Information we may collect includes name and email address, and phone number. 

In addition, when you visit our Sites some information may be automatically collected. For example, it is standard for your Web browser to automatically send information to every Web site you visit including ours. That information includes your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language, and referring Web site addresses. We may also collect information about your computer's operating system and information about your usage and activity on our Sites. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user-base as a whole. 

## Cookies

We may automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small data files that are stored on your hard drive by a Web site. Among other things, the use of cookies helps us to improve our Sites and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are most popular, to count the number of computers accessing our Sites, to personalize your experience, and to remember your preferences. 

We link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. If your browser is set not to accept cookies or if you reject a cookie, you may not be able to access certain features or services of our Sites. The use of cookies by our service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our service providers use session ID cookies to collect data in order to enable us to provide a better user experience. 

## Web Beacons

We and our third party partners use Web beacons that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Web beacons, also known as gifs, are electronic images that may be used on our Sites or in our emails. A Web beacon may be used on our Web pages to collect information, deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness, or in our emails to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon. We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications. 

## Use Of Personal Information We Collect

We use your personal information to provide you with services, to operate and improve our Sites and Applications, to send you messages, and for other purposes described in this Policy or disclosed to you on our Sites or in connection with our services. For example, we may use the information we collect from you on our Sites and Applications: 

  * to register for an account with us;
  * to apply to become a partner;
  * to personalize and improve your experience on our Sites and with our Applications;
  * to respond to comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * to deliver service messages and other services and content you request and to send information related to accounts and services, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * to send you information about new promotions, products, and services offered by iSpot and our selected partners; and
  * to conduct an aggregated analysis of the performance of promotions.

iSpot may store and process personal information in the United States and other countries. 

## Sharing Of Personal Information

We use third parties such as a credit card processing company to bill you for services, an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf, a company to provide our forums and an employment resources company to process your job applications. When you sign up for our services, we will share the personal information you provide only as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

We do not share your personal information with third parties other than as described above and as follows: 

  * with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers ("Service Providers") who are working on our behalf and need access to your information to carry out their work for us;
  * to (a) comply with laws or respond to lawful requests and legal process, (b) to protect the rights and property of iSpot, our agents, members, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use, or (c) in the good faith belief that disclosure is needed to respond to an emergency or protect the personal safety of any person; and
  * in connection with any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. In any such event, we will provide notice if your data is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

iSpot takes reasonable security measures to protect your personal information to prevent loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are impenetrable. 

If you use a password on our Site, you are responsible for keeping it confidential. Do not share it with any other person. If you believe your password has been misused, please advise us immediately. 

## Choices About Use Of Your Information

We use third parties such as a credit card processing company to bill you for services, an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf, a company to provide our forums and an employment resources company to process your job applications. When you sign up for our services, we will share the personal information you provide only as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

## Updating And Accessing Your Personal Information

If your personal information changes, we invite you to correct or update your information as soon as possible. You can request changes or access to your information by emailing [privacy@ispot.tv](mailto:privacy@ispot.tv). 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account, request that we no longer use your information to provide you services or delete your personal information, contact us at [privacy@ispot.tv](mailto:privacy@ispot.tv). We will respond to your request to have your personal information deleted within 30 days. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

## Links To Other Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of iSpot. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

## Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request that your testimonial be removed you may do so by emailing us at [privacy@ispot.tv](mailto:privacy@ispot.tv). 

## Public Forums

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs, community forums, and/or commenting systems. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum or commenting system, contact us at [privacy@ispot.tv](mailto:privacy@ispot.tv). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

## Social Media Features

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

## Changes To This Policy

iSpot may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date above. If there are material changes to this policy, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account). We encourage you to review this Policy whenever you visit our Sites or use our Applications to understand how your personal information is used. 

## Questions About This Policy

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at [privacy@ispot.tv](mailto:privacy@ispot.tv) or iSpot.tv, Inc., c/o Legal Dept., 14042 NE 8th Street Suite #108, Bellevue, WA 98007.
